Let's do a grocery meal hair update.
For context, this is my hair in the middle of April.
Erm, not great.
Erm, I've actually found this thing to be the only thing that's helping my hair.
So, erm, I don't use any of the dermal oils or anything,
so I can't hang on time. I just put it in my hands.
Ringing, bro. Ringing, erm, and just lather it through.
These are the areas that, that I need it the most.
So I just, we're looking a bit scraggly right now,
but I promise you, once it's washed, it'll be a bit better.
Erm, not a lot of products and things don't work for me.
I'm not gonna lie, but er, this, erm, I'll link this one below,
because this is the already diluted one.
You don't need to dilute this one.
Right, once I've been in the shower and washed this out, I'll show you.
Right, I'm drying my hair.
So, I'll be two seconds.
Right, my hair's dry.
Please, just pray that.
Like, I know it doesn't seem like a lot, but it really, really is.
And I don't know what, like, well, it's far acquired right now,
but don't worry, we're gonna style this.
Honestly, the difference that this has made, since losing my hair,
has been, like, ridiculous.
Like, I am literally just getting fullness throughout,
and I know it doesn't seem like it, because I've got barely anyhow as it is.
But, like, I can't tell you, like, that was bold.
You can't put hairs in that bit there.
Like, crazy.
I'm not gonna even sell it to you,
because the results speak for themselves.
This ain't even an ad, or I bought this with my own money.
Like, I genuinely bought it with my own money.
Yeah, I've linked it below anyway.
Do you think, or done, much of a difference to me.
But, my hair's getting thicker.
And I'll do my astals too soon.